[
    {
        "problem": "(1*2) + 1 =  ?",
        "correctResp": "TRUE",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "problem": "(1/1) - 1 =  ?",
        "correctResp": "FALSE",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "problem": "(7*3) - 3 =  ?",
        "correctResp": "TRUE",
        "answer": 18
    },
    {
        "problem": "(4*3) + 4 =  ?",
        "correctResp": "TRUE",
        "answer": 16
    },
    {
        "problem": "(3/3) + 2 =  ?",
        "correctResp": "FALSE",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "problem": "(2*6) - 4 =  ?",
        "correctResp": "FALSE",
        "answer": 6
    },
    {
        "problem": "(8*9) - 8 =  ?",
        "correctResp": "TRUE",
        "answer": 64
    },
    {
        "problem": "(4*5) - 5 =  ?",
        "correctResp": "FALSE",
        "answer": 11
    },
    {
        "problem": "(4*2) + 6 =  ?",
        "correctResp": "TRUE",
        "answer": 14
    },
    {
        "problem": "(4/4) + 7 =  ?",
        "correctResp": "FALSE",
        "answer": 12
    },
    {
        "problem": "(8*2) - 8 =  ?",
        "correctResp": "FALSE",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "problem": "(2*9) - 9 =  ?",
        "correctResp": "TRUE",
        "answer": 9
    },
    {
        "problem": "(8/2) + 9 =  ? ",
        "correctResp": "FALSE",
        "answer": 7
    },
    {
        "problem": "(3*8) - 1 =  ?",
        "correctResp": "TRUE",
        "answer": 23
    },
    {
        "problem": "(6/3) + 1 =  ? ",
        "correctResp": "TRUE",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "problem": "(9/3) -2 =  ?",
        "correctResp": "FALSE",
        "answer": 7
    }
]